

Mohammad Amir Jamali

aj3848110@gmail.com

Mashhad, Iran



21 September, 1991 iiii



Master's degree in IT and experience in different programming languages, as well as managing a startup. Besides programming, in particular, I am interested in researching about Quantum Computing, Machine Learning, and Auto Trading Systems. I hope to join an organization that truly helps its employees to better align their values and expand their expertise.

WORK EXPERIENCE

СТО

Enviroble.com

2021 - Now

London-UK

Founder/Senior Developer

Tradeoption.ir

Django Rest Framework, Celery, React, MQL Mashhad-Iran 2020

Developer

ckit.ir – Strapi (NodeJs)

2019 - 2020

Mashhad-Iran

Founder/Senior Developer

Class724.ir - WordPress

2017 - 2019 Birjand-Iran

Developer

gooani.com- WordPress

2016 - 2017 Mashhad -Iran

RESEARCHES

- Predicting Bitcoin price with Bayesian Neural Network by using COT weekly report (Master's thesis) 2019 **Python and MQL**
- Convergence of AI and CRM (European Conference on the Impact of AI and Robotics) 2020
- An introduction to Quantum Computing; Advantages and challenges

(6th National Conference on Distributed Computing and Big Data Processing) – 2021

EXPERTISE

- **Machine Learning** (Neural Networks and other Machine Learning techniques)
- **Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP 2008)**
- **Programming Languages:**
 - > JS: JavaScript, Node, React, AJAX, NextJs, Express
 - > PHP: WordPress Theme and Plugins Customization (Woocommerce, Stripe Connect, WC Vendor, Redis, Elastic Search, Creating Gutenberg Blocks, Elementor, WP CLI...),
 - Python: Web scraping (Scrapy, Selenium), Django (DRF, Redis, Celery, PyTest, Locust, Silk, Postgrsql)
 - MQL: Expert Advisor programing

FAMILIAR WITH



EDUCATION

Master's in Information Technology -Electronic Trade

Islamic Azad University

2017-2019

Bachelor's in Industrial Engineering

Payam Noor University

2009 - 2013

SKILLS



INTERESTS



LANGUAGES

English	Arabic	Farsi
Professional	Native	Native